strikeforce.com 2010-11-28

# Strikeforce | Mixed Martial Arts (MMA) | Fighters

**Privacy Policy**

Thisprivacy policy ("Privacy Policy") is applicable to the website of ExplosionEntertainment, LLC dba Strikeforce(herein collectively, "Explosion" "we", or "us"). The Strikeforce website operated by Explosion ("Operator") willbe referred to as the "Strikeforce Site". Explosion'spolicy is to respect the privacy of visitors and users of the Strikeforce Site (herein "you", "your" or "users"). Explosiondoes not sell, share or rent user personal information to others in any waythat we have not mentioned in this statement. Explosion uses reasonableprecautions to keep the personal information that you disclose when you browse,send or exchange emails, or make purchases or other uses of the Strikeforce Site. 

1\. **_Information We Collect._**

Except for the automatically collected information (described below) Explosiondoes not collect personally identifiable information about individual usersexcept when such information is provided on a voluntary basis. For example,personally identifiable information may be gathered from an entry into apromotion, contest or sweepstake, the registration process for subscriptionsites or services and in connection with content submissions, communitypostings (e.g., chat and bulletin boards), subscription to newsletters, subscriptionand use of our text messaging service, suggestions, emails, voting/pollingactivities and transactions when merchandise or services are ordered or bought.This information may vary but may typically include your name, home address,telephone number, e-mail address, age, date of birth, interests and forpurposes such as legal compliance. If you place an order on the 

Strikeforce Site, we may collect your credit card number(including the CVV code), expiration date, shipping, billing and otherinformation based on your purchase activity on the StrikeforceSite.

 _ _Automatically Collected Information:                    __  
You also should be aware that non-personal information and data (such as thepages you visit on the Strikeforce Site as well asyour IP address) may be automatically collected through the standard operationof Explosion's internet servers or through the use of "cookies". Cookies areused to identify Strikeforce Site visitors or membersso they do not have to re-enter an user ID and password, when, for example, themember wants to post a comment on a discussion board or order merchandise.Cookies help us improve user experience and display more prominently goods andservices that might interest you. If you do not have the cookies feature of yourbrowser enabled (and in most, if not all, browsers are enabled by default), youmay be required to enter your password each time you access Strikeforce'sSite, or any of the member features and you may not be able to access someinformation or features on the Strikeforce Site. 

Cookies are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users,facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site totrack usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvementsand targeted advertising. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique numberto the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. You should be awarethat Explosion cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting informationobtained by advertisers or third parties that manage or place advertisements orlinks on website, once you've clicked on an advertisement or link to anotherwebsite and have left our website, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and youmust read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personalinformation will be handled on their website. If you do not want suchinformation collected through cookies, there is a relatively simple procedurein most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature. However,you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you with certainfeatures (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the 

Strikeforce Site. If you decline acceptance of cookies, youmay experience less than optimal performance of the StrikeforceSite. 

2\. **_How We Use The Personally Identifiable And Other Information and Who we may Disclose Such Information to._**

Explosion may use your information to provide you with services and informationyou have requested or products you have purchased, to respond to specificinquiries made by you, to resolve any disputes or collect fees, to preventillegal or fraudulent activities, to comply with law, a governmental orjudicial order, to enforce the terms of use of the StrikeforceSite to improve our services; enforce any contest or sweepstake rules; protecta user's safety or security including the safety and security of property thatbelongs to a user; and/or protect our safety and security and the safety andsecurity of our websites, our affiliates and/or third parties, including thesafety and security of property that belongs to us, our affiliates or thirdparties.

If you place an order on the Strikeforce Site, wewill use your financial information to bill you for products and services orotherwise process your transaction. By making a purchase on the 

Strikeforce Site, you consent to us providing yourfinancial information to our service providers to process your transactions.These third parties may include credit card companies and banking institutionsused to process the transaction.

We may use this information for our internal business purposes, for example, totailor the Strikeforce Site content or to assess theamount of traffic to the Strikeforce Site. Explosionmay provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our visitors, trafficpatterns and related site usage information. This data reflects the 

Strikeforce Site usage patterns gathered during thousandsof user visits to the Strikeforce Site. Explosion mayalso provide log files and other databases of user information to third partiesfor analysis so that we may improve our content offerings, graphics, layout, ease of the StrikeforceSite use or navigation, and the like.

Further, notwithstanding any opt out of promotional information by you, Explosionreserves the right to contact you regarding account status, changes to thesubscriber agreement and other matters relevant to the underlying serviceand/or the information collected.

Explosion may disclose your information in special cases when in our solejudgment we have reason to believe that disclosing this information isreasonably necessary to identify, contact or bring legal or other correctiveaction against someone who may be misusing the StrikeforceSite or any of its features, for example, by inducing or causing injury to orinterference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights,reputation, identity, sensibilities or property of Explosion or its users, oranyone else that could be harmed by such activities. The law may require Explosionto share your personal and non-personal information (such as "Cookies"described above) pursuant to judicial or governmental orders, subpoenas orwarrants. Under such circumstances, Explosion reserves the rights to blockaccess to the Strikeforce Site to one or moreindividual users, close the Strikeforce Site and/ordisclose user information to the respective judicial or other governmentalauthority. In addition, Explosion reserves the right to use and disclose yourpersonal and non-personal information for purposes of investigating or takingaction relating to any illegal or fraudulent activities or other activitiesthat pose a threat to the physical safety of any person or for the violation ofthe terms of use of the Strikeforce Site or asotherwise required by applicable law.

For those participating in Sweespstakes sponsored by Explosion, participants agree,where allowed by law, all participants and winner(s) grant the Sponsor permissionto use their names, characters, photographs, voices, and likenesses inconnection with promotion of this and other sweepstakes and waive any claims toroyalty, right, or remuneration for such use.  Participants also agree that the Sponsor may disclosepersonal information obtained from participants in the Sweepstakes to thirdparties and use such information for marketing and other purposes.

 __

If you submit a text message to Explosion, we may broadcastthe content of the text message by means of our jumbotronduring a game.  The jumbotron may be filmedduring a game, and your text message may be rebroadcast over televisionnetworks and the Internet. Your text message may therefore be viewed by otherusers or the public.  We urge you to use good judgment and not textinformation that you do not want the general public to know.

Explosion may disclose your information to our employees, contractors,affiliates, distributors, dealers, vendors and suppliers who process suchinformation on our behalf, participate with us in the provision or operation ofthe Strikeforce Site or provide you with services.Information collected from you may be transferred to a third party as a resultof a sale or acquisition, or merger or any other transfer of assets transactioninvolving Explosion or one of its companies.

Explosion reserves the right to perform, or have performed by third parties,statistical and other analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order tomeasure interest in and use of the various pages, or functional, graphical orinformational frames or areas of the StrikeforceSite, and to inform advertisers of such analyses as well as the number of usersthat have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. Explosionwill provide only aggregated anonymous data from these analyses to thirdparties.

You should also be aware that Explosion may sometimespermit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based servicesthrough an Strikeforce Site. Such third parties havetheir own privacy policies that may differ from the policy of Explosion.Accordingly, Explosion is not responsible for any actions, policies or breachesof security or privacy of such third parties; users are urged to check theapplicable privacy policy of any such party to determine if it is acceptable tothe user before providing any personally identifiable information.

Additionally, through the Strikeforce Site you may beintroduced to or be able to participate in activities, subscribe for certainservices, text us messages or otherwise access or participate in promotions,including, without limitation, participation in contests or sweepstakes,subscription to newsletters or magazines, participation in voting/pollingactivities and other any activities or services (collectively, "Public Activities")sponsored or offered by Explosion or any Explosion sponsor, advertisers orthird parties (sponsors, advertisers and third parties collectively, "ThirdParties"). When you participate in such Public Activities, we may also shareyour personally identifiable information with Third Parties. We are notresponsible for the actions or policies of such Third Parties. You shouldreview the applicable privacy policy of such Third Parties before participatingin Public Activities to understand how your personal information may be used.Notwithstanding the foregoing, we currently do not knowingly allow childrenunder thirteen years of age to enter any Public Activities hosted by ThirdParties. Please see Section 10 for restrictions on children's participation in aPublic Activities. Users should also be aware that when they voluntarilydisclose personally identifiable information (e.g., name, image, e-mailaddress, home or work addresses or phone numbers, identity or creditinformation, or the like), through text messages, on bulletin boards or in chatareas of the Strikeforce Site(s), such information,along with any substantive information disclosed in the user's communication,can be collected, correlated and used by the Third Parties, Third Parties'bulletin board viewers or chat site participants, silent observers and membersof the public. Therefore, providing such information may result in unsolicitedmessages from, or other use by other posters or Third Parties. Such activitiesare beyond the control of Explosion, and Explosion is not liable for any harmto you by misuse of such information by Third Parties.

3\. **_Special Rules for Children under 13 Years_**

Federal law prohibits us from collecting any personal information from a childunder thirteen (13) years of age without the verifiable consent of such child'sparent. The statements in this Privacy Policy about the collection and use ofpersonal information shall also apply to treatment of personal informationobtained from children under 13 years of age, except that such children areprohibited from conducting any financial transactions on the 

Strikeforce Site, from participating in chat roomdiscussions. Explosion shall not disclose personal information relating to achild under 13 years of age to any third party. Inaddition, the added protection of the special rules promulgated under theChildren's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") shall apply to any personalinformation relating to children under 13 years ofage.

4\. **_Links to Third Party Web Sites_**

Please note that the StrikeforceSite may containlinks to web sites that are not operated by Explosion, such as any Explosionsponsor, Showtime Networks or various community or industry organizations. Explosionis not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites,or use of information you might provide these other sites. We recommendstrongly that you carefully review the privacy policy posted on each linkedother site that you use to determine whether that site's policies are acceptableto you before providing personally identifiable information. We cannotguarantee the security of any information you disclose to such other websitesand you do so at your own risk.

5\. **_User's Ability to Opt-Out_**

Beginning at the point of Explosion's first email or text message with theuser, and upon each subsequent email or text message, the user will have theopportunity to indicate whether he or she would like to "opt out" ofreceiving promotional and/or marketing information about other products, servicesand offerings from Explosion and/or any third parties. Upon such request, Explosionwill allow any user to "opt out" of further promotional contacts atany time. Additionally, upon request, Explosion will use reasonable efforts toallow users to update/correct personal information previously submitted whichthe user states is erroneous to the extent such activities will not compromiseprivacy or security interests. Also, upon a user's request, Explosion will usecommercially reasonable efforts to functionally delete the user and his or herpersonal information from its database; however, it may be impossible to deletea user's entry without some residual information because of backups and recordsof deletions.

The foregoing policies are effective as of June 6, 2010. Explosion reserves theright to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence ofa new Privacy Policy. This statement and the policies outlined herein are notintended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or onbehalf of any user, and use of the SVSE Site operates as full consent by eachuser to collection and use of user's personal information within the guidelinesand limitations outlined herein.

6\. **_Security Measures_**

Explosion has adopted generally acceptable security measures to protect yourpersonal information against loss, misuse and alteration when such informationis within Explosion's control. These services are stored in San Jose, CA forStriekforce.com and in the Chicago area for Singlehop.com hosted sites.

Please note that despite all precautionary steps, no data transmission over theInternet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Explosion will use commerciallyreasonable measures to protect your information but does not warrant that theinformation transmitted to us will be secure at all times.

7\. **_Your Obligations as a User_**

By using the StrikeforceSite, you signify your assent to Explosion's Privacy Policy. Please note that Explosionis the sole owner of all information collected during use of the 

Strikeforce Site. If you do not agree to this policy,please do not use the Strikeforce Site. Yourcontinued use of the Strikeforce Site followingposting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean that you accept the revisedPrivacy Policy.

If you accept this Privacy Policy, which is indicated by your continued use,you must always comply with the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy andany other terms and conditions posted on the StrikeforceSite. You will respect all intellectual property rights of SVSE and any thirdparties relating to the content on the StrikeforceSite or services provided through the StrikeforceSite (for example, photographs and newsletters).

You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your logininformation, including any passwords and user names. At no time will Explosionrequire you to transmit your password information to Explosion via email.Should you receive any such requests, please contact info@strikeforce.com toauthenticate such inquiry before responding to the same.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or about theuse of your personally identifiable information, you should first contact the Explosionvia email at webmaster@strikeforce.com.

8\. **_Governing Law  
_**  
Any disputes arising between Explosion and you inrelation to your use of the Strikeforce Site shall begoverned by the laws of the State of California, without regard to its choiceof law provisions and the federal and state courts located in San Jose,California shall have exclusive jurisdiction over all claims.

9\. **_Amendment Procedure and Questions Regarding this Privacy Policy_**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If weamend this Privacy Policy to permit material changes in the way we collect, useand/or share your personal information, we will notify you of such changes bysending you an e-mail at the last e-mail address that you provided to us,and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. Any suchmaterial changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective thirty (30) calendardays following either our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or our posting ofnotice of the changes on our website. Any such material changes to this PrivacyPolicy may affect our use and sharing of personal information that you providedto us before our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish topermit material changes in our collection, use or sharing of personalinformation that you have provided to us before the effective date of suchchanges, you must so notify us before that effective date. Please be advised,however, that, regardless of whether you provide such notice to us, the changesto this Privacy Policy will apply to any personal information that you provideto us on or after the effective date of such changes. Notwithstanding theforegoing, any changes to this Privacy Policy that materially affects themanner in which we collect and use personal information relating to childrenunder thirteen (13) years of age will become effective in relation to eachchild only pursuant to receipt of written consent from the parent of such achild. To the extent that such material changes are necessary for continuedaccess to a service on the Strikeforce Site, failureto receive parental consent may result in the child not being able to accesssuch a service. Questions regarding this statement should be directed to thePrivacy Policy Coordinator, Legal Department, Explosion Entertainment, LLC, 

525 West Santa Clara Street, San Jose, CA 95113.

10\. **_Children's Privacy Statement (users under 13 years old)_**

Explosion and its affiliates take our responsibilities to our younger visitorsseriously and intend to fully comply with the requirements of the Children'sOnline Privacy Protection Act and the Guidelines promulgated by the Children'sAdvertising Review Unit of the Better Business Bureau.

  * In general, we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 via the Strikeforce Site, such as in our fan chat rooms.

  * In the future we may offer children the opportunity to participate in Public Acivities (defined above) via the Strikeforce Site. To participate in Public Acivities on the Strikeforce Site, children will be required to print a paper entry form from the Strikeforce Site along with a copy of this Privacy Policy (which will be attached to the entry form) and have their parents sign and mail or fax the form to us. The parent's submission of the entry form indicates the parent's acceptance of our collection and use of personal information about their child. A child's parent has the option to consent to the collection and use of their child's personal information without consenting to the disclosure of that information to third parties, but if such disclosure is necessary to make available a service which has been requested, then the child will not have access to such service. Children will not be permitted to provide personal information via the Strikeforce Site or to sign up for Public Activities online.

 _ _Information Collected.__  
Information collected about a child could include personal information such asname, email address, address and age of a child. Explosion will not ask formore information than reasonably necessary for participation in the activitychosen by the child. A parent can review his or her child's personalinformation by accessing the child's preferences. In addition, a parent caninstruct Explosion to delete, stop collecting or using his or her child'spersonal information by contacting webmaster@strikeforce.com

 _ _Use of Information Collected.            __  
Explosion will use the personal information collected about a child to providethe child with the special services for which he or she has registered, as wellas fulfilling a requested transaction, record keeping or marketing back to thechild. The child will not be permitted to participate in chat rooms.

 _ _Disclosure.__  
Explosion and the Operator will maintain the confidentiality, security andintegrity of the personal information collected about a child and suchinformation will not be disclosed to any third parties.

All questions about our policies related to children's data and our datasharing practices should be directed to webmaster@strikeforce.com
